Trump says Governor J.B. Pritzker and Mayor Brandon Johnson should be in jail.
ICE officers' lives are in danger in Chicago, and at this point, they're aiding and abetting
an insurrection.
This is nothing more than sabotage and a dereliction of duty.
But the mayor says Trump's just trying to lock up another brother.
It's certainly not the first time that Donald Trump has called for the arresting of a black
man, unjustly.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to stay firm.
Johnson's not very bright.
Trump also wants to lock up the white guy.
But the white guy's building a wall.
This is a convicted felon, I mean, think about that, who is threatening to jail me.
I got to say, this guy's unhinged, he's insecure, he's a wannabe dictator, and there's one thing
I really want to say to Donald Trump, if you come for my people, you come through me.
So come and get me.
Jamie Back's big, but he's not that big.
How's ribs going to stop a chopper?